Okay, so right now
you've researched the niche,
you've got viewers, loves
and hates, and title
structures and formats they
really seem to be
into. What we need
to do now is
update Cynthia's brain. So
what I want you
to do is this.
If you are a
new or small channel,
and you had no
outliers when we originally
built Cynthia's brain in
phase one, you now
have a big list
of them. So I
want you to double
check that final list
we made that took
all of the channels
you've been analysing and
turned it into one
databank. And just make
sure the AI didn't
write anything silly or
weird in there. Then
what we want to
do is we want
to take that list,
and we want to
make it 12 titles
long. And we put
them on a Google
Doc, we make the
text big like this,
put some space between
them, screenshot it, and
load it into Cynthia's
brain in the image
section. Now there's a
reason we use an
image here, which I'm
not going to bore
you with, but please
do it that way.
Now what you have
is an MVP brain,
which we're going to
build up over time
as we learn more
and more lessons from
posting content and failing
as fast as you
can. I also want
you to look at
the top three problems.
That this information brought
up when we analysed
it, and ask, is
that similar to the
ones I came up
with originally when I
was doing the business
research? If it's very
different, you might want
to make a call.
Go with what the
research from YouTube told
you, or go with
the initial research you
did. Again, don't worry
or overthink this. Indecision
right now is worse
than no decision. The
only way we can
discover the right path
is to take action.
So you will refine
this over time with
our fail as fast
as you can system,
but you just need
to make this call
right now. Now if
you're an experienced user,
you might want to
make a call to
Cynthia. If you're an
experienced business, I would
go more by the
business data you had.
If you did the
business research from Reddit
or Google or blogs,
I would go more
by the YouTube data.
Now, if you were
an experienced YouTube channel
and you had tons
of outliers on your
channel, which you put
up that list of
12 with, what you
could now do is
pick and choose. Delete
some of the titles
from your list and
add in some of
the new ones from
the outliers you researched,
or just leave it
the same. What we
don't want to do
is take away the
things that grew your
business. What we don't
want to do is
take away the things
that grew your channel
because leaving that is
going to put viewers
off. The only reason
we do that is
if we're repositioning. And
now what you have
is your version one
of Cynthia's brain and
guardrails set up. It's
going to be like
your avatar giving you
feedback. And as you
learn things over time,
you'll update this. And
as you have more
of your own outliers,
you'll add them to
the list. So this
list just continually evolves.
In fact, in six
months time, it shouldn't
look the same as
it now is. If
it is, you're not
learning enough. Now, one
last thing to note.
We don't want 100
titles on that list.
I kept it to
12 for a reason.
Don't go over. You
can also fill out
your avatar demographic information
at the top now
based on your dream
buyer too, if you've
not already done that.
And then move on
to the next video
where you're going to
start ideating.